http://www.mbusi.com/index.php/site-privacy

Team Zone
HomeCCPA request formccpa opt out request form pageMBUSIContact InfoEmployment/CareersVisitor Center/Museum/ToursOwner Support (MBUSA.COM)Corporate InfoFacts & FiguresDiversityEmploymentPhilanthropyMBUSI RetireesScholarshipsEnvironmental InfoLocation & DirectionsProducts GLS-SUV GLE-SUV GLE Coupe Owners SupportFactoryThe Body ShopThe Paint ShopAssemblyTest TracksPhoto GalleryPlant ToursVisitor CenterPlant ToursInside the Visitor Center Location & DirectionsContact InfoCareersTrainingCo-op ProgramMechatronics ProgramMercedes Tech ProgramInternational Internship ProgramHiring Status Careers at DaimlerLogin
Privacy
Mar 262015
MBUSI Privacy Notice
Rev: JANUARY 2020
Mercedes-Benz U.S. International, Inc. ("MBUSI”) appreciates your interest in its products and your visit to its Internet site, MBUSI.com (the "Site"). Your privacy is important to us and we want you to feel comfortable visiting our Site. Protecting your privacy in the processing of your personal data is an important concern to which we pay special attention. Therefore, this privacy notice tells you about the information MBUSI collects through the services available on our Site, how we use that information, and how you can opt out of certain uses of information we may collect. By using our services and accessing our Site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy notice, as modified from time to time by us. If we decide to change this privacy notice, we will post a new privacy notice on our Site and change the date at the top of the privacy notice. Therefore, we encourage you to check the date of our privacy notice whenever you visit this Site for any updates or changes. Our Site may include, however, links to other websites that are not covered by this privacy notice. These sites have their own privacy and information security notices and terms and conditions. Please review the privacy notices and terms and conditions sections of such websites for additional details.
ACCESSING AND UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION
Freedom of Choice
If you do not want your Personal Information to be made available to any third party, please contact us at
so we can block your data accordingly. Note, however, that certain services and/or functions of our Site may not be available if you elect to block your Personal Information. Further, if, in connection with your use of a particular service, we ask to use your Personal Information in a way not described in this privacy notice and you do not wish to permit that use, you can choose not to use that particular service. Otherwise, your use of such service will be your consent to the use of your Personal Information in the way described.
Email Communication
You will only receive email from MBUSI if you are a Team Member and/or you have requested a response. If you are a Team Member and currently on our Toolbox mailing list and would prefer not to receive further information from us, you may login to this website and go to the (Team Zone Toolbox page) and uncheck the “Toolbox Notification” box.
Your California Privacy Rights
California residents are afforded certain privacy rights regarding the collection and use of their personal information. Please click here for an explanation of California residents’ privacy rights and how to exercise those rights.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
Our Site is a general audience site that is not designed nor intended to collect Personal Information from children under the age of 18. MBUSI does not knowingly collect or maintain any Personal Information from children under the age of 18. In addition, no part of this Site is designed with the purpose of attracting any person under age 18. To respect the privacy of children and to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, children under the age of 18 should not provide any Personal Information on this Site. We ask that parents supervise their children while online.
IP Address and Click-Stream Data Collection
MBUSI may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data for market research, for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you access the Internet. Our servers identify your computer by its IP address. When you request web pages from our Site, our servers log your IP address.
Click-stream data is information collected by our servers when you request pages from our Site. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view, and other such Non-Personal Information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at our Site, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content, and the like.
Security
MBUSI uses commercially reasonable efforts to store and maintain Personal Information to protect it from loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction by any unauthorized party. We encrypt order information, including credit card numbers, using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to ensure that our customers' information is safe as it is sent over the Internet to our server.
We exercise reasonable care to protect your Personal Information. This includes storing the Personal Information on our servers behind a secure firewall and ensuring all transmissions to other vendors use secure encryption technology. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. So while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us or receive from us. This is especially true for information you transmit to us via email. We have no way of protecting that information until it reaches us. Once we receive your transmission, we maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your Personal Information.
When registering for access to a secure area of our Site, we will ask you to select a Username and Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. We will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also, remember to sign out of the registered area of our Site and close your browser window when you have finished.
Internally, we will limit access to Personal Information to those persons who need the information to provide products and services to you or maintain or service those products or services. These persons are limited in number and are committed to our privacy and security policies. We will review our security arrangements from time to time, as we deem appropriate.
Links to Other Sites
Please be aware that we provide links to third-party sites as a service to our visitors, and that we are not responsible for the content or information collection practices of those sites. Please note that these sites´ privacy policies may differ from those of MBUSI. We encourage you to review and understand their privacy practices before providing them with information.
Privacy Statement Revisions
A revised privacy notice will only apply to data collected subsequent to its effective date on this version of our Site. Any revisions will be posted at least seven days prior to its effective date.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT
We collect several types of information on our Site. Personal information is information that identifies an individual or is directly associated with a specific person, such as a customer´s name, mailing address, telephone number, email address, credit card number, or information about activities which can be directly linked to that person, such as his or her purchases (e.g., personal information - note: MBUSI is not an ecommerce site and does not capture credit information). Our definition of Personal Information does not include “aggregate” information. Aggregate information is data about use of our Site, such as pages visited on our Site. Aggregate information helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new products and services, and tailor existing products and services to customer desires.
We may also collect "Non-personal Information", which is information about you that does not itself identify you individually.
Collection of Personal Information
When you use certain parts of our Site, we collect certain kinds of Personal Information:
Team Member Account Setup: To set up a Team Member Account, we ask applicants to provide a valid MBUSI employee badge number and the name of their immediate supervisor. In order to set up a Team Member Account, we require applicants to provide a valid email address, as well as create a unique Username and Password. In addition, this area allows you to receive personalized MBUSI news and information via email. When you register for Team Member access, we may collect various kinds of Personal Information including your name, email address, home address, and phone number. We also collect and store access information related to your account, including Username and Password.
Social Interaction: We may collect information that identifies you personally when you submit comments, questions, or suggestions through various user interfaces within our Site content.
Use of Personal Information
We do not sell or disclose information that identifies our visitors personally or makes it possible for other parties to contact them directly without our visitors’ consent. We may use, sell, disclose, or otherwise dispose of Personal Information we collect in the following circumstances:
Email Inquiry: We use the information you provide about yourself during Email Inquiry to contact you regarding your inquiry. We do not share this information with parties other than the appropriate MBUSI personnel you have specified or are best suited to respond to your inquiry.
Response to Inquiries: We use return email addresses to answer the email inquiries we receive. We may also use these email addresses to provide follow-up, and to respond to queries.
Online Profile: If you choose to create an Online Profile or receive products or information, or to otherwise give us Personal Information, we may store some or all of that information and use it for marketing research and marketing purposes, which may include sharing it with other MBUSI authorized personnel, research, or other services for us. To enhance your experience on our Site, we might use information you provide to us through your Online Profile to pre-populate forms with your name, address, phone number, and email address.
Companies that work for or with MBUSI: We may, without notice to you, share Personal Information with companies that work for us for the sole purpose of providing you with services or information you’ve requested or already have through our Site. These companies may assist us in fulfilling your requests or processing your information. In addition, we may share Personal Information with companies that work for us to provide verification or other services. We enter into contractual agreements with these companies prohibiting them from disclosing or using this information other than to carry out the purposes for which the information was disclosed. These companies are in no way authorized to sell, rent, or trade your Personal Information. While there are such contractual obligations in place, we cannot and do not guarantee that a third party will not breach its contractual obligation and use your Personal Information in a way contrary to this privacy notice.
Legal Requirements: We may disclose Personal Information: (a) to conform with the law, respond to claims, or comply with legal process served on MBUSI or its affiliates (e.g., a lawful subpoena, warrant, or court order); (b) to enforce or apply our policies or agreements (including to initiate, render, bill, and collect for amounts owed to us); (c) to protect and defend our or our visitor´s rights or property, the Site, our employees, visitors, or the public; or (d) if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay.
Use of Non-Personal and Aggregate Information
We may use non-personal and aggregate information to better design our Site and share with our marketing and advertising agencies.
COOKIES
Privacy Policy
CA PRIVACY STATEMENT
Disclaimer
Terms of Use
Sitemap
Team Zone Home Services Events Toolbox
HomeCCPA request formccpa opt out request form pageMBUSIContact InfoEmployment/CareersVisitor Center/Museum/ToursOwner Support (MBUSA.COM)Corporate InfoFacts & FiguresDiversityEmploymentPhilanthropyMBUSI RetireesScholarshipsEnvironmental InfoLocation & DirectionsProducts GLS-SUV GLE-SUV GLE Coupe Owners SupportFactoryThe Body ShopThe Paint ShopAssemblyTest TracksPhoto GalleryPlant ToursVisitor CenterPlant ToursInside the Visitor Center Location & DirectionsContact InfoCareersTrainingCo-op ProgramMechatronics ProgramMercedes Tech ProgramInternational Internship ProgramHiring Status Careers at DaimlerLogin
